<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Government Final</title>
    <link>https://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Government Final</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:19:26 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Citizens and Government Action</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/citizens-and-government-action/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:19:26 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/citizens-and-government-action/</guid>
      <description>United States citizens have duties and responsibilities, duties are required, and responsibilities are not. Our duties are to obey laws, pay taxes, serve in the military when requested, and go to jury when requested. Our responsibilities are to vote, be informed, take part in government, help your community, and respect other’s rights. Regions are an area with at least one common characteristic which differentiates it from the others. Mayland has five regions which are western Maryland, which is rural and has a lot of mining, capital, which has a wealthier population and is near DC, central which is densely populated and has a lot of business with the Chesapeake Bay, eastern, which has a lot of tourism and crab hunting, and there is southern, which is developing currently and is very agricultural.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Economics</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 21:16:04 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/economics/</guid>
      <description>Economics is how people use their scarce resources for their wants and needs and how goods and services are produced and distributed. We have three types of resources, natural, human, and capital. Natural resources are the ones found in nature, human resources are people doing work, and capital resources are goods made by us that can be used multiple times and allow us to make more resources with them. We have a limited amount of these resources, so we need an economic system to distribute them to people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Judicial Branch</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/judicial-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:42:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/judicial-branch/</guid>
      <description>The judicial branch interprets the laws made by the legislative branch. They also decide on citizens&#39; innocence when it comes to crimes committed and settle disputes between groups of people. Civil cases are when there are disputes between parties and the court must decide on who is right. The two types of cases are tort and breach of contract. A tort is when one party (the plaintiff) sues the defendant for damages (usually money) and a breach of contract is when the defendant breaks a contract that they agreed on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Executive Branch</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/executive-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:36:01 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/executive-branch/</guid>
      <description>The executive branch is the leaders of the country like the presidents and the governors.   Caucus and primaries occur, which is where candidates are chosen to run for president. A caucus is when the party members meet to select a candidate. A primary is where citizens vote for a candidate with ballots. The two types of primaries are open and closed. Open is where anybody can vote for anyone regardless of political affiliation, and closed is where you can only vote for your party.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Legislative Branch</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/legislative-branch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 19:32:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/legislative-branch/</guid>
      <description>The legislative branch is the branch that makes and carries out laws. It is divided into two chambers which are the Senate and the House of Representatives. The senate has 100 members, two per state, and they represent the whole state. The leader of the senate is the Vice President, and the senate can confirm presidential appointments and ratify treaties. The house of representatives has 435 members spread out based on each state&amp;rsquo;s size.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Constitution</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/the-constitution/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:28:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/the-constitution/</guid>
      <description>The Articles of Confederation were the first guiding document for the new country. However, this document had many problems such as congress being unable to collect taxes, which made them powerless and poor. Trade also could not be regulated, making it difficult since every state had different tariffs and laws. Laws could not be enforced, so everybody was breaking them. New laws needed 9/13 states for approval, so decisions were rarely made.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Types of Government</title>
      <link>https://example.org/post/types-of-government/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 17:04:06 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.org/post/types-of-government/</guid>
      <description>The main three types of government are monarchy, democracy, and dictatorship. A dictatorship is where one or more individuals have all control over everything such as China and North Korea. A democracy is where the people have the power by electing leaders that fit their needs. A monarchy can be a form of either of the two, an absolute monarchy is where the king or queen has all control, and a constitutional monarchy is where the king or queen has limited powers and there are other branches where people make decisions.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
